

Neha Bhardwaj

Graphic Designer
3D Artist

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Contact: 9711836787

Email: nbhardwaj28@gmail.com

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Project Management &

Coordination

Technical Drawings

SOFT SKILLS

Communication

Creativity

Enthusiastic

Keen Learner

Interpersonal Skills

SOFTWARE AND TECHNOLOGY

Illustrator

Photoshop

MS Office-PowerPoint, Word

and Excel

Corel

3ds Max

After Effects

AutoCad

Award-winning, AAASP certified 3d Interior Designer with 7+ years of experience in Graphic designing. Adept in analysing requirements, project planning towards delivering the right design efficiently while keeping quality as a priority. Working in alignment with company's goals and mission and exploring every opportunity to use my skills and experience. Effective communicator with experience in managing clients and articulating complex concepts.

CERTIFICATIONS

- Graphic Designing Certification
- Web Designing Certification
- o 2D Animation Certification
- o 3D Animation Certification

EXPERIENCE

Project Manager – HBA International Pvt. Ltd.

2016-2019

- o Delivered inspiring, efficient interior designs for commercial and residential markets
- o Exceeded milestones and earned several satisfied designers
- o Created high-quality designs efficiently in a fast-paced environment
- Project coordination and work breakdown between the onsite and offshore teams
- Created quality proposals for customer submission including, but not limited to, scope & requirements, design, assumptions and dependencies

Senior Rendering Artist – HBA International Pvt. Ltd.

2014-2016

- o Rendered awe-inspiring interiors for residential and commercial clients
- Project coordination and lead for small projects
- Used CAD to create 40+ high-end, compelling interiors
- o Received 99% positive client feedback in exit interviews

Chief Modeler - HBA International Pvt. Ltd.

2012-2014

- Created accurate and proportionate models' development-furniture carving details, draperies, antique sculptures etc.
- Led a team of Modellers of 10 members
- o Coordinating with Rendering Artist for capturing detailed requirements

Junior Modeler - HBA International Pvt. Ltd.

2011-2012

o Development of near real models including fabrics, Cushions, furniture etc.

Freelance Projects

2019-2020

- 3d Interior Designing & rendering for Unify Systems Private Limited Dec 2015 Mar 2020
- 3d interior designing for Aleomandra Resort, Mykonos, Greece with
 London based Designers

Feb 2020 - Mar 2020 Oct 2019 - Dec 2019

- o Interior designing of a Cafeteria, namely YANGKIEZ, for KUDOS POP
- London based Project Nottingham View

Oct 2019

Office interior with Alpine Modular Interiors Pvt. Ltd.

Aug 2018 - Jan 2019

EDUCATION

- o Earned scholarship in Sanskrit in 2007 and 2008 from Delhi Sanskrit Academy
- O Participated in Inter College Sanskrit Language Competition
- Higher Secondary (CBSE) with 73.5% from Delhi Jain Public School 2004
- 10th Standard (CBSE) with 55% from Delhi Jain Public School

2002

ADDITIONAL ACTIVITIES

- Winner of Women Carom Championship twice
- Taught Graphic Designing to BPL Children, to contribute in their career, for 6 months in a
 NGO, Deepalaya Corporate Office
- Active participation in and conducting team building exercises on a periodic basis